Guide to the Sam di Bonaventura papers, 1900-1998
George Mason University Libraries
Special Collections and Archives, George Mason University
Sam di Bonaventura papers
1900-1998
George Mason University. Special Collections and Archives.
Sam di Bonaventura
C0070
181.5 linear feet (159 boxes)
Collection consists of notebooks containing related research notes, scholarly papers, concert programs, musical scores and sheet music arranged alphabetically by subject.
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
Collection is open to research.
Acquisition Information
Collection donated by Sam di Bonaventura in 1984-1998.
Biographical Information
Sam di Bonaventura was a professor of music at George Mason from 1975 until 1998. Known around campus simply as "Dr. Sam," di Bonaventura taught music history, music theory, and private violin lessons until he retired in spring 1998. Di Bonaventura studied music at Juilliard, Yale, Harvard, and Peabody Conservatory. He studied composition with musical giants including Robert Ward, Vincent Persichetti, Paul Hindemith, Walter Piston, and Benjamin Lees. He was a professional violinist and composed a number of original works for orchestra, chamber ensemble, vocal and choral media.
Scope and Content
Collection consists of notebooks containing related research notes, scholarly papers, concert programs, musical scores and sheet music arranged alphabetically by subject.
Arrangement
This collection is organized alphabetically by composer or subject.
Adjunct Descriptive Data
Related Material
Di Bonaventura's extensive recorded music collection was added to the George Mason University Libraries' media collections.
Index Terms
Persons:
Di Bonaventura, Sam, 1921-1998.
Subjects:
Music.; Music--Instruction and study.; Music theory.
Contents List
- Dr. Sam di Bonaventura papers
  - 11th-12th Cent. I (Box 1)
    Contents: Notes, Musical Scores, Articles Headings: 1.Compositional practice, 2.Conductus, 12th-13th cent., 3.Ecclesiastical Drama, 12th cent. 4.Historical: 9-12th cent., 5.Instruments (EMPTY), 6.Lauda, 7.Mass, 8.12th cent., Misc., 9.Monophony, Sacred, 11th cent., 10.Monophony Secular, 10th-12th cent.11.Motet, 12th cent., 12. Notation, 11th-12th cent., 13.Performance Practice, 12th cent. 14.Polyphony 11th-12th cent. Date(s) of materials:?
  - 11th-12th Centuries II [1996] (Box 1)
    Contents: Notes, Articles, Scholarly papers, Assignments Headings: 1.Religion, 2.Sources, 3.Summary 12th cent., 4.Theoretical Date(s) of materials:1966, approx.
  - 13th Century I (Box 1)
    Contents: Notes, Musical Scores, Articles Headings: 1.Cantiga, 2.Clausula, 3.Compositional Practice, 4.Conductus, 5.Unlabled Misc.: Anon: Estampie, Anon: Conductus, Anon: Te Deum, 13th c. Liturgical Drama, 13th c. Ecclesiastical Drama, 6.Historical, 7.Geislerlieder (EMPTY), 8.Hocket, 9.Instrumental (EMPTY), 10.Unlabled: Instruments, Medieval Date(s) of materials:?
  - 13th Century II (Box 1)
    Contents: Sample tests, Notes, Musical Scores, Articles\ Headings: 1.Monophony, 2.Motet, 3.Notation, 4.Performance Practice, 5.Polyphony, 6.Lauda, 7.Mass, 8.Misc., 9.Sacred Misc. Date(s) of materials:?
  - 13th Century III (Box 2)
    Contents: Notes, Musical Scores, Articles Headings: 1.Secular Misc., 2.Sources, 3.Summary, 4.Theoretical, 5.Tropes and Sequences Date(s) of materials:?
  - 14th Century A (Box 2)
    Contents: Sample Exams, Notes, Musical Scores, Articles Headings: 1.Ballade, 2.Caccia, 3.Compositional Practice, 4.Historical: 14th cent., 5.Instrumental, 6.Instruments, 7.Lauda (EMPTY), 8.Madrigal, 9.Mass, 10.Misc., 11.Motet, 12.Notation, 13.Performance Practice Date(s) of materials:?
  - 14th Century B (Box 2)
  - 15th Century I (Box 2)
    Contents: Notes, Articles, Musical Scores Headings: 1.Compositional Practice, 2.Historical 15th cent., 3.Unlabled: Canti, Carols, Historical 15th cent. Date(s) of materials:?
  - 15th Century II (Box 3)
    15th Century II Contents: Notes, Articles, Musical Scores, Scholarly Papers, Charts Headings: 1.Instrumental, 2.Mass, 3.Unlabled: 15th cent. Misc., 4.Motet, 5.Notation, 6.Performance Practice, 7.Sacred Misc. Date(s) of materials:?
  - 15th Century III (Box 3)
    15th Century III Contents: Notes, Articles, Musical Scores, Scholarly Papers Headings: 1.Secular Misc., 2.Sources, 3.Summary, 4.English Music, 5.Flemish Music, 6.German Music, 7.Italian Music, 8.Spanish Music, 9.Unlabled: Theoretical 15th cent., Tinctoris, Date(s) of materials:?
  - 16th Century I (Box 3)
    Contents: Notes, Articles, Musical Scores, Illustrations Headings: 1.Anthem, 2.Chanson, 3.Chorale, 4.Unlabled: 16th cent. Compositional Practice, 5.Dance (EMPTY), 6.Frottola, 7.Historical, 8.Instrumental Date(s) of materials:?
  - 16th Century B (Box 3)
    Contents: Notes, Articles, Musical Scores, Scholarly Papers, Concert Programs Headings: 1.Lied, 2.Madrigal, 3.Madrigal Comedy, 4.Mass, 5.Miscellaneous, 6.Motet, 7.Notation, 8.Passion, 9.Performance Practice Date(s) of materials:?
  - 16th Century C (Box 4)
    Contents: Notes, Articles, Musical Scores, Scholarly Papers, Illustrations Headings: 1.Program Music, 2.Psalms, 3.Publishers, 4.Quodlibet, 5.Religion, 6.Sacred Misc, 7.Sacred Misc., 8.Sources, 9.Suite, 10.Summary, 11.Theoretical Date(s) of materials:1968-
  - 16th Century Inventories of MSS (Box 4)
    Contents: Musical Scores, Inventories Headings: 1.British Museum 38539, 2. Brogynton MS.27, 3.Cambridge Dd.2.11, 4.Cambridge Dd 5.78.5, 5. Cambridge Dd.9.33, 6.Edinburgh Univ. Dc.5.125, 7.Trinity Coll., Dublin D.1.21 Date(s) of materials:?
  - 16th Century Inventories of Prints (Box 4)
    Contents: Inventories Headings: 1.Petrucci Motet Prints, 2.Antico Motets (1520-21), 3.Petreius Motets (1538), 4.Moderne Motets (1532), 5.Mantanus-Neuberus Motets (1540), 6.Du Chemin Motets (1554) Date(s) of materials:?
  - 16th Century Catalogues (Box 4)
    Contents: Notes, Catalogues Headings: 1.Unlabled: A Catalogue of French Chansons, 2.Montanus Neuberus, 3.Unlabled: Petrucci Motet Prints Date(s) of materials:?
  - 18th Century B (Box 4)
    Contents: Notes, Articles Headings: 1.Orchestral, 2.Overture, 3.Performance Practice, 4.Programme Music, 5.Religion, 6.Sacred, 7.Song, 8.Sonata, 9.Suite, 10.Summary, 11.Symphony, 12.Theortical, 13.Variation, 14.Vocal Date(s) of materials:?
  - 19th Century A (Box 5)
    Contents: Notes, Articles, Musical Scores Headings: 1.American Music, 2.Ballet, 3.Choral, 4.Compositional Practice, 5.Concerto, 6.Chamber, 7.Conductors, 8.Historical, 9.Instrumental, 10.Keyboard, 11.Literary, 12.Misc., 13.Opera, 14.Oratorio, 15.Orchestral Date(s) of materials:?
  - 19th Century B (Box 5)
    Contents: Notes, Articles, Musical Scores, Illustrations Headings: 1.Performance Practice, 2.Programme Music (EMPTY), 3.Religion, 4.Sacred, 5.Sonata, 6.Suite, 7.Summary, 8.Symphony, 9.Theoretical, 10.Tone Poem, 11.Variation (EMPTY), 12.Vocal Date(s) of materials:?
  - 19th Century Concerto (Box 5)
    Contents: Notes, Articles, Musical Scores Headings: 1.Sociology, 2.Comparison, 3.Characs (EMPTY), 4.Repertory, 5.Beethoven, 6.Chart, 7.20th C., 8.Repertory (EMPTY) Date(s) of materials:?
  - 19th Century Concerto (Box 5)
    Contents: Notes, Musical Scores, Charts, Scholarly Papers Headings: 1.Unlabled: The Romantic Concerto, 2.Unlabled: Mendelssohn Violin Concerto, Op.64, 3.Unlabeled: Beethoven Piano Concerto No.4, Op.58, 4.Unlabeled: Lalo Op.21 "Symphonie Espagnole," 5.Unlabeled:19th cent. notes Date(s) of materials: ?
  - 1st-10th Centuries (Box 6)
    Contents: Notes, Articles, Musical Scores, Illustrations Headings: 1.Compositional Practice, 2.Unlabeled: Historical 1st-10th cent., 3.Instruments, 4.Mass, 5.Misc., 6.Monophony, 7.Unlabeled: Notation, 8.Polyphony, 9.Religion, 10.Theoretical Date(s) of materials:?
  - 20th Century (Box 6)
    Contents: Notes, Musical Scores, Sample Assignments Headings: 1.Unlabeled: Music in 20th Century, 2.2nd Semester, 3.Isms, 4.Post Romant., 5.Nationalism, 6.Schoenberg, 7.Bartok, 8.Debussy, 9.Stravinsky, 10.Webern, 11.Milhaud, 12.Copland, 13.Berg Date(s) of materials: 1964-65
  - 20th Century (Box 6)
    Headings: 1.Unlabeled: Music History: 22, 2.History, 3.Introduction, 4.Formal Paper (EMPTY), 5.Composers, 6.20th Cent. Trends, 7.Primitivism, 8.Microtonalism, 9.Exoticism, 10.Post-Romanticism, 11.Computer Music, 12.Pandiatonicism, 13.Impressionism, 14.Post-Impress. Date(s) of materials:?
  - 20th Century (Box 6)
    Contents: Notes, Articles, Scholarly Papers, Illustrations, Syllabi Headings: 1.Biblio., 2.Introduction, 3.Isms, 4.Composers, 5.Pandiatonicism, 6.Microtonalism, 7.Cubism, 8.Neo-Classicism, 9.Atonalism, 10.Aleatoricism, 11.Electronicism, 12.Instrumental Exploration, 13.Jazz, 14.Misc. Date(s) of materials: 1987
  - 20th Century (Box 7)
    Contents: Articles on 20th Century Composers from [a] textbook(s) Headings: 1.Unlabeled Date(s) of materials:?
  - 20th Century (Box 7)
    Contents: Notes, Articles, Scholarly Papers, Illustrations Headings: 1.Jazz, 2.Futurism, 3.Impressionism, 4.Expressionism, 5.Nationalism, 6.Electronicism, 7.Neo-Classicism, 8.Post-Impressionism, 9.Minimalism, 10.Post-Romanticism, 11.Scriabin, 12.Fauvism, 13.Computer, 14.Exoticism, 15.Verism Date(s) of materials:?
  - 20th Century A (Box 7)
    Contents: Notes, Articles, Charts, Concert Programs Headings: 1.Americana, 2.Ballet, 3.Chamber (EMPTY), 4.Choral, 5.Composers, 6.Compositional Practice, 7.Concerto, 8.Historical, 9.Incidental Music, 10.Instrumental, 11.Piano Music, 12.Literary, 13.Mass (EMPTY), 14.Misc. Date(s) of materials:?
  - 20th Century B (Box 7)
    Contents: Notes, Articles Headings: 1.Notation, 2.Oratorio, 3.Orchestral, 4.Overture, 5.Performance Practice, 6.Programme Music, 7.Sacred, 8.Sonata, 9.Suite, 10.Summary, 11.Symphony, 12.Theoretical, 13.Tone Poem (EMPTY), 14.Variation (EMPTY), 15.Vocal Date(s) of materials:?
  - 20th Century Concerto (Colby) (Box 8)
    Contents: Notes, Articles, Musical Scores, Inventories Headings: 1.Woodwind, 2.Brass, 3.Strings, 4.Percussion, 5.Keyboard, 6.Names, 7.Multiple, 8.Voice, 9.Special, 10.Jazz, 11.Examples Date(s) of materials:?
  - 20th Century Pianists [1958-] (Box 8)
    Contents: Articles in alphabetical order about 20th cent. pianists Headings: 1.Unlabeled Date(s) of materials: [1958-]
  - Africa [1967, 1972-] (Box 8)
    Contents: Notes, Articles, Illustrations Headings: 1.Africa, 2.Africa, North 3.Algeria, 4.Egypt, 5.Libya (EMPTY), 6.Morocco, 7.Sudan, 8.Tunisia, 9.United Arab Republic (EMPTY), 10.Java Date(s) of materials: [1967,1972-]
  - Art: Medieval-20th Cent. (Box 8)
    Contents: Notes Headings: 1.Medieval, 2.Renaissance, 3.Baroque, 4.Classical, 5.Romantic, 6.20th Century 7.Misc. Date(s) of materials:?
  - Asia I 1967- (Box 8)
    Contents: Notes, Articles, Illustrations Headings: 1.Asia, 2.Afghanistan, 3.Bhutan (EMPTY), 4.Borneo, 5.Brunei (EMPTY), 6.Burma, 7.Cambodia, 8.Ceylon, 9.Cyprus (EMPTY), 10.Formosa (EMPTY), 11.Hong Kong (EMPTY), 12.Indonesia, 13.Iran, 14.Iraq (EMPTY), 15.Israel, 16.Jordan (EMPTY), 17.Korea Date(s) of materials: 1967-
  - Asia II (Box 9)
    Contents: Notes, Articles Headings: 1.Kuwait (EMPTY), 2.Laos, 3.Lebanon (EMPTY), 4.Malaysia (EMPTY), 5.Malaya, 6.Macao (EMPTY), 7.Mongolia, 8.Nepal, 9.Pakistan, 10.Philippines, 11.Sarawak (EMPTY), 12.Saudi Arabia (EMPTY), 13.Singapore (EMPTY), 14.Syria, 15.Thailand, 16.Tibet, 17.Vietnam, 18.Yemen Date(s) of materials: 1970-
  - A-T Misc. (Box 9)
    Contents: Notes, Articles, Scholarly Papers, Illustrations Headings: 1.Arrangement, 2.Caricature, 3.Christmas, 4.Composites, 5.Dance, 6.Historym, 7.Humor, 8.Instruments, 9.March, 10.Royalty, 11.Texts, 12.Records, 13.Genesis Date(s) of materials: -1982
  - Bach (Box 9)
    Contents: Notes, Articles Headings: 1.Unlabeled (Articles on Bach), 2.I-Bach:Biography, 3.II, 4.III, 5.IV-Keyboard Music, 6.V-Keyboard Music, 7.VI-Keyboard and Choral Music, 8.VII-Mass, 9.VIII-Complete Works Date(s) of materials: ?
  - Bach A-Fa (Box 9)
    Contents: Notes, Articles, Musical Scores Headings: 1.Bibliography, 2.Biography, 3.Canon, 4.Chaconne, 5.Chamber Music, 6.Chorale, 7.Complete Works, 8.Dance Dates of materials: 1971, 1985-
  - Bach Cantata I 1973, 1982- (Box 10)
    Contents: Notes, Articles, Musical Scores Headings: 1.1-19, 2.20-29, 3.30-39, 4.40-49, 5.50-59, 6.60-69 Date(s) of materials: 1973, 1982-
  - Bach Cantata II 1972, 1978 (Box 10)
    Contents: Notes, Articles, Musical Scores Headings: 1.70-79, 2.80-89, 3.90-99, 4.100-109, 5.110-119, 6.120-129, 7.130-139, 8.140-149, 9.150-159, 10.160-169, 11.170-179, 12.180-189, 13.190-199, 14.200-209, 15.210-219, 16.220-229 (EMPTY), 17.230-239, 18.240-249 Date(s) of materials: 1972, 1978
  - Bach Cantata III 1972- (Box 10)
    Contents: Notes, Articles, Musical Scores Headings: 1.Unlabeled:"Gott, der Herr, is Sonn' und Schild," 2.Misc. Date(s) of materials: 1972-
  - Bach Concerto 1943, 1977- (Box 10)
    Contents: Notes, Articles, Musical Scores Headings: 1.Brandenburgs, 2.Brandenburg No. I, 3.Brandenburg No. II, 4.Brandenburg No. III, 5.Brandenburg No. IV, 6.Brandenburg No. V, 7.Brandenburg No.VI, 8.Clavier, 9.Clavier in A, 10.Clavier in D, 11.Clavier in E (EMPTY), 12.Clavier in F (EMPTY), 13.Clavier in f, 14. Clavier in g, 15.2 Clavier in C, 16.2 Clavier in C, 17.3 Clavier in C, 18.3 Clavier in d, 19.4 Clavier in a, 20.Clav/Fl/Vn, 21.Italian, 22.Misc., 23.Oboe/Violin, 24.Violin in a, 25.Violin in E, 26.Two Violins Date(s) of materials: 1943, 1973, 1977-
  - Bach Family 1954, 1975- (Box 1)
    Contents: Notes, Articles Headings: 1.Bach, Johann Christof (1642-1703), 2.Johann Christoff Friedrich, 3.Bach, Johann Ernst, 4.Johann George, 5.Johann Phillip 6.Bach, John Michael (1648-94) (EMPTY), 7.Bach II, J.S., 8.Bach, W.F., 9.Bach, W.F.E. Date(s) of materials: 1954, 1975-
  - Bach Family 1954, 1981 (Box 11)
    Contents: Notes, Articles, Musical Scores Headings: 1.Carl Phillip Emanuel, 2.Gottlieb Friedrich, 3.Bach, Heinrich (1615-92), 4.Bach, Johann Christoff (1735-82) Dates of materials: 1954, 1981
  - Bach Fu-Ma 1978, 1990 (Box 11)
    Contents: Notes, Articles, Musical Scores Headings: 1.Fantasia, 2.Fugue, 3.Instrumental Misc., 4.Invention, 5.Keyboard Music, 6.Lute Music, 7.Magnificat, 8.Mass Dates of materials: 1978, 1990
  - Bach Mi-Or 1962, 1980- (Box 11)
    Contents: Notes, Articles, Musical Scores, Concert Programs Headings: 1.Misc., 2.Motet, 3.Musical Offering, 4.Oratorio, 5.Orchestra Music, 6.Organ Music Dates of materials: 1962,1980-
  - Bach Pa-Pr 1962, 1979- (Box 12)
    Contents: Notes, Articles, Musical Scores Headings: 1.Partita, 2.Passacaglia, 3.Passion, 4.Prelude Dates of materials: 1962, 1970, 1979-
  - Bach R-Z 1973, 1983- (Box 12)
    Contents: Notes, Articles, Musical Scores Headings: 1.Ricercar, 2.Sonata, 3.Style, 4.Suite, 5.Toccata, 6.Variation 7.Transcription Date(s) of materials: 1973, 1977, 1983
  - Banchieri/Bellini 1966- (Box 12)
    Contents: Notes, Articles, Musical Scores Headings: 1.Banchieri, 2.Unlabeled: Bellini Date(s) of materials: 1966-
  - Barber 1966- (Box 12)
    Contents: Notes, Articles, Musical Scores, Scholarly Papers, Concert Programs Headings: 1.Ballet, 2.Biography, 3.Chamber Misc. (EMPTY), 4.Choral Misc., Complete Works, 6.Concerto, 7.Letters (EMPTY), 8.March (EMPTY), 9.Misc. (EMPTY), 10.Opera, 11.Orch. Misc., 12.Overture, 13.Piano Music, 14.Prelude (EMPTY), 15.Quartet (EMPTY), 16.Serenade (EMPTY), 17.Sonata (EMPTY), 18.Song, 19.Song Cycle, 20.Style, 21.Symphony, 22.Toccata, 23.Variation (EMPTY) Dates of materials: 1966-
  - Baroque (Composers) 1965, 1977- (Box 13)
    Contents: Notes, Articles, Musical Scores, Charts Headings: 1.Complete Works, 2.Composers, 3.Bach, 4.Corelli, 5.Handel, 6.Lully, 7.Monteverdi, 8.Purcell, 9.Vivaldi Date(s) of materials: 1965, 1969, 1977-
  - Baroque (Instr. 1) 1970- (Box 13)
    Contents: Notes, Articles, Musical Scores Headings: 1.Canzona, 2.Capriccio, 3.Consort Music, 4.Fantasia, 5.Fugue, 6.In Nomine Dates of materials: 1970-
  - Baroque (Instr. 2) 1969, 1978- (Box 13)
    Contents: Articles, Notes, Musical Scores Headings: 1.Partita, 2.Prelude, 3.Ricercar, 4.Sonata, 5.Suite, 6.Toccata, 7.Tombeau, 8.Variation Date(s) of materials: 1969, 1976, 1978-
  - Baroque (Instr. 3) (Box 13)
    Contents: Notes, Articles, Musical Scores, Syllabi Headings: 1.[Class] 1, 2.[Class] 2, 3.[Class] 3, 4.[Class] 4, 5.[Class] 5, 6.[Class] 6, 7.[Class] 7, 8.[Class] 8, 9.[Class] 9 Date(s) of materials:
  - Baroque (Instr. 4) 1947, 1977- (Box 14)
    Content: Notes, Articles, Musical Scores Headings: 1.Instrumental, 2.Keyboard, 3.Lute, 4.Instruments, 5.Style (EMPTY), 6.Performance Practice, 7.Compositional Practice, 8.Wind Music Dates of materials: 1947, 1967, 1970, 1976, 1977-
  - Baroque (Misc.) 1965, 1969- (Box 14)
    Contents: Notes, Articles, Musical Scores Headings: 1.Historical, 2.Arts, 3.Literary, 4.Misc., 5.1968 Course, 6.Theoretical Date(s) of materials: 1965, 1969-
  - Baroque (Opera) 1970, 1976- (Box 14)
    Contents: Articles Headings: 1.Opera Date(s) of materials: 1970, 1976-
  - Baroque (Opera/Oratorio) 1969, 1976- (Box 14)
    Contents: Notes, Articles, Musical Scores, Inventories Headings: 1.Opera, 2.Oratorio Date(s) of materials: 1969, 1971, 1976-
  - Baroque (Orchestral) 1967, 1976- (Box 15)
    Contents: Notes, Articles, Musical Scores Headings: 1.Orchestral, 2.Overture, 3.Concerto Date(s) of materials: 1967, 1970, 1976-
  - Baroque (Vocal) 1967, 1969- (Box 15)
    Contents: Notes, Articles, Musical Scores, Inventories Headings: 1.Unlabeled (Baroque Misc.), 2.Cantata, 3.Chorale, 4.Lute Song, 5.Lied, 6.Madrigal, 7.Madrigal Comedy, 8.Mass, 9.Motet, 10.Passion, 11.Sacred Misc. Dates of materials: 1967, 1969-
  - Baroque I 1970, 1990- (Box 15)
    Contents: Notes, Articles Headings: 1.Unlabeled: The Baroque, 2.Unlabeled: Requiem, 3.Unlabeled: Terminology, 4.Unlabeled: History of the Baroque, 5.Unlabeled: Chronology of Events and Musicians in Baroque Period, 6.Unlabeled: Chronology of the Baroque, 7.Unlabeled: Oratorio, 8.Italian, 9.French Date(s) of materials: 1970,1990
  - Baroque II 1963- (Box 15)
    Contents: Notes, Articles, Musical Scores Headings: 1.Baroque, 2.Topics, 3.Recordings, 4.Orchestra:History, 5.String Instrument Makers, 6.Orchestra: Seating, 7.Orchestra:Instruments, 8.Orchestra:Sound, 9.Orchestra:Score, 10.Orchestra:Organizations/Conds, 11.Orchestra:Show-Pieces, 12.Orchestra: Hall, 13.Vocal Forms, 14.Mass:Text, 15.Bach:Biography, 16.Cantata:Description, 17.Bach:Cantata, 18.Oratorio:Definition, 19.Mendelssohn:Oratorio, 20.Bach:Fugue, 21.Bach:Magnificat, 22.Handel:Concerto, 23.Suite:Definition, 24.Bach:Suite, 25.Handel:Suite, 26.Motet. 27.Venice, 28.Figured Bass, 29.Chamber Music, 30.Sonata, 31.Bach:Sonata, 32.Bach:Partita Date(s) of materials: 1963
  - Baroque III 1968 (Box 16)
    21. Baroque III Contents: Notes, Articles, Musical Scores, Lecture Notes Headings: 1.July 11:Music in Baroque, 2.July 12, 3.July 15:Exam, 4.July 16:Chamber Music, 5.July 17:Chamber Music, 6.July 18:Chamber Music, 7.July 19:Chamber Music, 8.July 22: Chamber Music, 9.July 23:Orchestral Forms Date(s) of materials: 1968
  - Baroque IV (Box 16)
    Contents: Notes, Musical Scores Headings: 1.Baroque XI:Baroque Instruments, 2.Baroque XII:Baroque Instruments, 3.Baroque XIII:Baroque Instruments, 4.Baroque XIV:Baroque Instruments, 5.Baroque XV:Baroque Instruments, 6.Baroque XVI:Bar.Instr., 7.Baroque XVII:Bar.Instr., 8.Unlabeled:Baroque Instruments XVIII, 9.Baroque XIX:Bar. Instr., 10.Baroque XX: Bar. Instr., 11.Baroque XXI:Bar. Instr. Date(s) of materials: ?
  - Baroque V 1950, 1977- (Box 16)
    Contents: Articles, Musical Scores, Scholarly Papers Headings: 1.General, 2.Summary Date(s) of materials: 1950, 1967, 1977-
  - Baroque VI (Box 16)
    Contents: Notes, Musical Scores Headings: 1.July 24 (Overture), 2.Unlabeled (July 25), 3.July 26 (Overture), 4.July 29, 5.July 30, 6.July 31, 7.August 1, 8.August 2, 9.August 5, 10.August 6 Date(s) of materials: ?
  - Baroque VII 1959, 1969- (Box 17)
    Contents: Notes, Articles, Musical Scores Headings: 1.Overture, 2.Performance Practice, 3.Prelude-Fugue (EMPTY), 4.Programme Music, 5.Religion, 6.Ricercar, 7.Sacred Misc., 8.Secular Misc., 9.Sonata, 10.Sources Date(s) of materials: 1959, 1969-
  - Bartok (Concerto) [1946-1976] (Box 17)
    Content: Notes, Articles, Musical Scores, Scholarly Papers Headings: 1.Misc., 2.Orchestra, 3.Piano No.1, 4.Piano No.2, 5.Piano No.3, 6.Two Pianos, 7.Viola, 8.Violin No.1, 9.Violin No.2 Date(s) of materials: 1946, 1962, 1971, 1976
  - Bartok I [1967-1986-] (Box 17)
    Contents: Notes, Articles Headings: 1.Ballet, 2.Bibliography, 3.Biography, 4.Cantata, 5.Chamber Music, 6.Choral Music Dates of materials: 1967, 1976, 1980, 1986-
  - Bartok II [1966-1980-] (Box 17)
    Content: Notes, Articles, Musical Scores, Scholarly Papers Headings: 1.Piano Music, 2.Quartet, 3.Rhapsody, 4.Sonata, 5.Song, 6.Style, 7.Suite, 8.Tone Poem Date(s) of materials: 1966, 1967, 1980-
  - Bartok III [1963-1987-] (Box 18)
    Content: Notes, Articles, Musical Scores Headings: 1.Complete Works, 2.Dance, 3.Divertimento, 4.Etude, 5.Fantasia (EMPTY), 6.Instrumental Music, 7.Letters, 8.Literary, 9.Misc., 10.Opera, 11.Orchestral Misc. Date(s) of materials: 1963, 1970, 1976, 1985, 1987-
  - Beethoven A-Ca [1936-1979-] (Box 18)
    Content: Notes, Articles, Illustrations Headings: 1.Aria, 2.Bagatelle (EMPTY), 3.Ballet, 4.Bibliography, 5.Biography, 6.Cantata Date(s) of materials: 1936, 1969, 1970, 1979-
  - Beethoven Ca-I [1960-1981] (Box 18)
    Content: Notes, Articles, Musical Scores Headings: 1.Camber Music, 2.Choral Misc., 3.Complete Works, 4.Dance, 5.Fantasia, 6.Fugue (EMPTY), 7.Incidental Music, 8.Instrumental Misc. Dates of materials: 1960, 1969, 1979, 1981-
  - Beethoven Concerto I [1968-1980] (Box 18)
    Content: Notes, Articles Headings: 1.Misc., 2.Piano I, 3.Piano II, 4.Piano III, 5.Piano IV Date(s) of materials: 1968, 1973, 1980-
  - Beethoven Concerto II [1935-1981] (Box 19)
    Content: Notes, Articles, Musical Scores Headings: 1.Piano V, 2.Triple, 3.Violin Date(s) of materials: 1935, 1968, 1976, 1980, 1981-
  - Beethoven K-Mi [1960-1980] (Box 19)
    Content: Notes, Articles, Illustrations Headings: 1.Keyboard Music, 2.Letters, 3.Literary (EMPTY), 4.March (EMPTY), 5.Mass, 6.Misc. Date(s) of materials: 1960, 1973, 1980
  - Beethoven Op-So [1902-1981] (Box 19)
    Content: Notes, Articles, Illustrations Headings: 1.Opera, 2.Oratorio, 3.Orchestral Misc., 4.Overture, 5.Quartet, 6.Quintet, 7.Romance, 8.Rondo (EMPTY), 9.Septet, 10.Sextet, 11.Song Dates of materials: 1902, 1907, 1964, 1970, 1981-
  - Beethoven Sonata [1967-1984] (Box 19)
    Content: Notes, Articles, Musical Scores Headings: 1.Cello, 2.Misc., 3.Piano, 4.Sonatina, 5.Violin Date(s) of materials: 1967,1970, 1976, 1984
  - Beethoven St-Z [1962-1985-] (Box 20)
    Content: Notes, Articles, Musical Scores Headings: 1.Style, 2.Tone Poem (EMPTY), 3.Transcription, 4.Trio, 5.Variation Date(s) of materials: 1962, 1985-
  - Beethoven Symphony I [1970-1981] (Box 20)
    Content: Notes, Articles Headings: 1.Misc., 2.No. 1, 3.No. 2, 4.No.3, No.4, No.5 Date(s) of materials:1970, 1976, 1979, 1981-
  - Beethoven Symphony II [1968-1981] (Box 20)
    Content: Articles, Notes, Musical Scores, Illustrations Headings: 1.No. 6, 2.Unlabeled (No. 7), 3.No. 8, 4.No. 9, Wellington Date(s) of materials: 1968, 1973, 1975, 1981-
  - Berg [1963-1980] (Box 20)
    Content: Notes, Articles, Musical Scores, Concert Programs Headings: 1.Aria, 2. Bibliography (EMPTY), 3.Biography, 4.Complete Works, 5.Concerto, 6.Letters, 7.Literary, 8.Misc., 9.Orchestral Misc., 10.Quartet, 11.Sonata, 12.Song, 13.Style, 14.Suite Dates of materials: 1963, 1967, 1976, 1980-
  - Berg Opera [1959-1984] (Box 21)
    Content: Notes, Articles (English and Italian), Scholarly Papers, Concert Programs Headings: 1.Opera, 2.Lulu, 3.Wozzeck Dates of materials: 1959, 1965, 1967, 1984
  - Berlioz A-N [1965-1976-] (Box 21)